This commission isn't all that impressive.
今回の依頼はたいしたことじゃない
We're going to sell guns to the local mafia.
地元のマフィアな人に銃器を売ります
Three trucks worth, which we'll drive to them.
トラック3台分　陸路
Normally I wouldn't touch a job that
brings in such small pocket change.
普通だったら　私はこんなお小遣い程度のやまは踏みません
It's not like I'm President Curry.
カリー社長じゃあるまいし
But we have a huge deal selling
missiles coming up in a week!
でも１週間後　ミサイル大口取引があります
You could say this is meant
to pull us through till then.
それまでの繋ぎと言ったところだ
As always, I'll need you to guard
the cargo and the transaction site.
あなたたちにはいつもどおり
貨物　現場の警備を…
Even though this is a low-end job,
those guys are jumpy.
安い仕事といっても
相手はドキドキしている
Be careful not to provoke them.
Especially you, Lutz!
刺激しないように
特にルツ
Eh?! You think I provoke people, Little Lady?
ウェッ　俺って刺激物なのか　お嬢
アー　ココ
Koko?!
Were you listening to me, Valmet?
話を聞いていたかね　バルメ
No, I don't think you were.
いや　聞いていなかっただろう
You looked like your mind
was 1,000 meters away.
千メートル望遠の目をしていたから
I'm sorry, Koko. I was spacing out.
すみません　ココ
ボーッとして
Well, I don't mind.
ま　いいんだけどね
We have always stood on the borderland.
我們始終踱步於境界線之上
I'm enjoying the view from here.
皆因此境風景獨好
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe...
Eeny,meeny,miny,moe...
一，二，三，四...
much the same
其實都一樣
We have always stood on the borderland.
我們始終踱步於境界線之上
日聽   貓日和
框框
I'm enjoying the view from here.
皆因此境風景獨好
翻譯  TL舊民
時軸  ZZZ
後期   aoi
神
島
魔
惡
&
諸
Pike or shield?
Pike or shield?  負けたくはない　でも傷つけたくもない
矛 or 盾？ 不想認輸 可是又不願受傷害
I don't want to lose,
but I don't want to hurt anyone either
I took it so I could confirm
手に取って　確かめてた
先挑一樣在手中仔細掂量
That there's definitely no going back
きっと戻れないんだって
可是發現再要反悔為時已晚
Whose side are you on?
你選的是哪邊？
(Don't want to know!) Memories are shackles
Don't want to know!  思い出は枷
Don't want to know!  思念是枷鎖
(Don't want to know!) A postscript love
Don't want to know!  後付けのlove
Don't want to know!  追悔莫及的愛
(Don't want to know!) Your kindness is a disservice
Don't want to know!  優しさは仇
Don't want to know!  溫柔是弱點
We have always stood on the borderland.
我們始終踱步於境界線之上
With your arms out wide, keep balanced
広げる両手　keep balance
張開雙臂保持平衡
Go the direction that lets you fly higher
より高く飛べる方へ
向著更高的天空振臂而飛
I want to protect
守りたいよ 僕らの翼のないこの背中に背負った
唯獨想保護的是.. 背負於我們那折翼的背膀之上的
What our wingless backs here bore:
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真實 & 夢想
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真實 & 夢想
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真實 & 夢想
I returned home by myself
after losing all of my subordinates.
部下を全員殺害され　一人帰国
I was hounded by their death reports
and work from the inquiry board.
全員分の戦死報告書
査問委員会質疑に追われた
Just after that, a pure-white girl
with an unearthly aura appeared.
直後現れた超俗的な雰囲気の
真っ白い少女
My first impression of her was horrible.
第一印象は最悪だった
Major Sophia Velmer of the Mechanized
Jaeger Squad, UNFID, FRDF.
FRDF　UNFID
機械化猟兵中隊・中隊長
ソフィア・ヴェルマー少佐
お若くして異例の階級です
That's an unusually high rank for one so young.
努力されたんですね
You must have worked hard.
わ…若…
I-I'm young?
Please! I'm an old lady compared to you.
そんな…あなたに比べたらおばさんですよ
What's with this kid?
何　この子
What is she doing inside a military institution?
どうして軍施設の中にいる
And she even knows my name!
それに私の名を
I imagine belonging to a family of
military elites must have spurred you on.
エリート軍人のお家柄ということもあなたを奮起させたのでしょうか
Your grandfather fought
and survived in the Winter War
お祖父様は「冬戦争」「継承戦争」を戦い抜いた方面軍中将
and the Continuation War as
the lieutenant general in a field army.
Your father is currently a lieutenant general
お父様は現役中将
as well as the National Defense
Command Center's Chief of Staff.
国防司令部参謀総長
He is a candidate to become
the next Commander-in-Chief.
次期軍総司令官候補
お兄様は中佐
Your big brother is a lieutenant colonel
and Captain of the Utti Jaeger Regiment.
ウッティ猟兵連隊大隊長
Unfortunately, you fell from grace while in Africa.
あなたは残念ながらアフリカで失脚なされた
Who are you, young lady?
あなた何者ですか お嬢さん
After undergoing an experience akin
to walking along the edge of Hell,
地獄の淵を歩いたような経験が過ぎた後
the major has two keys in her hand.
少佐の手には二つの鍵がある
One is a house key.
ひとつは家の鍵だ
Your family will probably gently
embrace you since you have been injured.
ご家族は傷ついたあなたを優しく包むだろう
"Forget your past and
enjoy a quiet life, Sophia."
過去を忘れて静かに生きろ　ソフィア
"Sophia, I'll introduce you to a wonderful man."
ソフィア　素敵な男性を紹介するわ
"Why don't you start a family of your own?"
そろそろ家庭に入ってはいかが
人間らしいいい生き方だ
It's a good, human-like way to live.
But your face says you blame
yourself more than you do your foes.
でもあなたって敵以上に自分を責める顔
There is a chance that you will slowly
break in that warm, homey environment.
温かい家庭で緩やかに壊れる可能性もなきにしもあらず
And what is the other key?
もう1つは何だって言うんですか
A key to the world.
世界の鍵だ
平和維持軍にあなた方は命を賭して
You risked your lives
for the Peacekeeping Force,
yet what did you actually manage
to do for that small country in Africa?
いったいあのアフリカの小国に何を与えることができたのか
Who was your enemy?
敵の正体は
What did he want so badly that he
would attack the United Nations Army?
国連軍を襲撃してまで　敵は何をほしがったのか
家の鍵？
The house key? Absurd!
バカな
部隊の？軍隊の鍵？
A unit key? An army key?
Even a key to your nation won't answer that.
国家の鍵を使っても無理だ
If you use a key to the world,
you may eventually find your answer.
世界の鍵を使って
やっと答えを知ることができるかもしれないな
Won't you come with me, Valmet?
私と一緒に来ないか　バルメ
Koko...
ココ
毀滅之丘 phase.1
"The Hill of Doom phase.1"
最悪だ　最悪だ
This sucks. It sucks!
It's hot and it stinks!
熱いしくさいし
And it's noisy.
うるさいし
Grégoire!
グレゴワール
ちょん切り過ぎだ
You're going overboard "clipping" him.
だからあっという間にくさくなるんです
That's why they start to stink so fast!
だって　ボスドミニク
But Boss Dominique, he got a hit in!
コイツ俺に１発当てた
もう死んでる
He's already dead. You're just wasting time.
時間の無駄です
リリアーヌ
Liliane!
まだいそうな気がする
I get the feeling there's
some left, Boss Dominique!
ボスドミニク
そんなバカな
That's ridiculous!
How many did you kill?
何人やりましたか
I got three!
あたし３人
俺も３人
I killed three, too.
俺も３人で終了です
I also killed three, so we're done. Pull out!
撤収
最悪だ
This sucks. How many minutes does it
take to bring down a gang's hangout?
暴力団の詰め所落とすのに何分かけるんですか
詰めが甘い　リリアーヌ
You lack follow-through, Liliane!
ちょん切らなくてもいい　グレゴ
You don't have to clip him, Grég!
We won't get any money until we
knock off the politician linked to that gang.
あの暴力団と繋がりのあった政治家をやってはじめて金になります
ああ　過酷な労働に見合わぬギャラ
Man, tough physical labor isn't my thing.
殺し屋ってな　つくづく俺に向いてない
I'm really not cut out to be an assassin.
That's not true, Boss Dominique!
そんなことないよ　ボスドミニク
It didn't bug me when I was young,
若いころは平気だったんですが
最近血の匂いがだめになってきまして
but lately I can't stand the smell of blood.
Grég's quite the cook.
グレゴの料理はなかなかのもの
それを生かして食堂を…と考えまして
I was thinking we could make the most
of that and start up a restaurant.
レストラン？
A restaurant?!
レストランだって　グレゴ
He said we're gonna run a restaurant, Grég!
Grég and I aren't suited for working
out front, so you'll be the waitress.
グレゴと俺は客前に出れる顔じゃないから
お前が給仕をやるんだ
That might be fun!
それはいいかもね
Thinking of our funds reminded me,
our next job pays well.
軍資金で思い出したんですが
次の依頼はギャラがいい
それだけ強いってことでしょう
That means they're all strong, you know?
場所はアレクサンドリア
Location: Alexandria.
Target: An arms dealer.
標的は武器商人です
Huh? Valmet?
あれ　バルメ
バルメー
Valmet?!
目的地に着いたのか　バルメ
Have you reached your destination, Valmet?
ヨナ君 ついてきちゃったんですか
Jonah?! You came with me?!
That Valmet girl has gone missing.
いなくなっちまったなぁ　バルメの奴
そうね
Indeed.
でも部下が一人や二人消えても　私の仕事は続く
But my job will continue on even
if a subordinate or two vanishes.
おい　今日は月曜日  新しい１週間が始まる
Hey, today is Monday.
A new week is just beginning.
お気楽ですけどね
We might be laidback,
but I am everyone's owner!
私はあなたたちのオーナー
そしてレーム
And Lehm! You are the president
in charge of the PMC.
あなたはPMCを束ねる社長だ
あなたにも責任があるんじゃないの
Doesn't some of this
responsibility lie with you?
言いたいことはわかるぜ　ココ
I know what you're getting at, Koko.
Including the bit about responsibility.
責任もな
だがな　言いながら君はこうも思ってる
But even as you're saying
this, you're also thinking,
必ず来ると予期していた日が来たんだ
"The day I knew would come has arrived."
Right?
だろう
Where's Jonah?!
ヨナは？
だめだ　お嬢
No luck, Little Lady!
We can't find him anywhere.
どこにもいねぇ
We can't get in touch with him, either!
連絡も通じねぇ
Jonah's missing, too!
ヨナ坊も消えた
アネゴについていったんだ
He went with the Chief.
恐らくな
Probably.
A-Are you okay? Calm down, Little Lady!
大丈夫か 落ち着くんだ　お嬢
落ち着いてます
I am calm!
二人とも必ず帰ってくる　ココさん
Both of them are sure to come back, Koko!
分かってます
I know!
さぁ　仕事に出発するよ
Now let's head off to work.
準備できてる　の
You'd better be ready!
こんな日もあるさ
There are days like this, too...
Jonah, please return to
Koko and the others. Please.
ヨナ君　ココたちの元へ帰ってください
お願いします
I can't do that.
それはだめだ
ヨナ　あなたのためを思って言ってるんだ
Jonah!
I'm saying this for your own good!
僕はココのことを思ってついてきたんだ
I came along because I thought
that would be best for Koko.
いろいろなことと引き換えにココの手下になった
In exchange for some stuff,
I became Koko's crony.
だから　ココに一番いいように行動にする
As such, I do what I think is best for Koko.
Valmet, you don't plan on coming back,
do you? That's how it looked to me.
バルメはもう帰えってこないつもりじゃないか そう見えた
それはココにとってまずいことだろ
Wouldn't that be bad for Koko?
ココの部隊は誰も欠けてはいけないんだ
Koko's unit can't lose
a single one of its members.
この子…
This boy...
You want to take revenge on those
guys we met in South Africa, don't you?
南アフリカであった連中がバルメの敵なんだな
An informer named Schokolade
started hanging around Koko
南アフリカからココに付き纏い
はじめたショコラーデっていうと言う情報屋
after our trip to South Africa.
あいつに調べさせたんじゃないか
Did you have her look into them
without informing Koko?
ココにも内緒で 南アフリカの連中のボスのこととか
Check out the boss over
those guys in South Africa?
いろいろと驚きました
You're full of surprises.
I still don't know anything about you, do I?
わたしはヨナ君のこと　まだ何にも知らなかったんですね
僕も手伝うよ　バルメ
I'll help you, Valmet.
そんなに一度に言わないで
Don't say so much all at once.
考える時間をください
Please give me some time to think.
I'm sorry I punched you.
殴ってごめんなさい
シャワーを浴びて冷やしましょう
Let's take a shower to cool that off.
This sucks.
最悪だ
見ましたか　資料
Did you see the file?
I did!
見た
ギャラの高さに納得です
The price matches the job.
Finishing them off is going
to be a real pain in the butt.
コイツらやるのは相当な骨ですよ
I'm impressed the arms dealer
managed to gather these guys up.
武器商風情がよくもまあ　集めたもんです
Ex-Delta Force? Ex-FRDF?
元デルタ？
元FRDF？
原FRDF？
Finnish Rapid Deployment Force：芬蘭快速反應部隊
この二人は化け物級だな
這兩個人是怪物級的
These two are ranked at the
monster level. Save them for later.
あとまわし
先擺一邊！
There is also an ex-cop
from an anti-terrorist unit
他にも元警察対テロ部隊　元自衛隊員
其他還有原警察反恐部隊和原自衛隊員
and a former member of the JSDF.
What's the JSDF?
自衛隊って何
自衛隊是什麼呀
日本の軍隊
日本的軍隊
Japan's army.
コイツは元イタリア軍　ボスニアヘルツェゴビナ紛争に行っている
這傢伙是原意大利軍 參加過波黑戰爭啊
This guy used to be part of the Italian army.
He fought in the War in Bosnia and Herzegovina.
知ってますか
你們知道嗎？
You know? They're the ones who wear
black feathers around here on their helmets.
ヘルメットのここに黒い鳥の羽をつけて戦う
頭頂著插上黑鳥羽毛的鋼盔去打仗的貨
插黑鳥羽毛的鋼盔：意大利軍代表了狙擊兵部隊（Bersaglieri）的黑色公雞羽毛裝飾。
Boss Dominique, you know so much about them!
ボスドミニクは詳しいね
ああ　コイツらヤバ過ぎます
These guys are too dangerous.
This just popped into my head,
but let's kill them off one at a time.
今思いついたんですが
一人ずつ殺しましょう
--We'll split this job into ten parts.
--I think that sounds good.
十回に分けての仕事です
それはいいと思う
どうしました　リリアーヌ
What is it, Liliane?
Check this guy out! Ugo! Ugo's a riot!
コイツを見て
ウゴ ウゴ面白い
It says he's ex-mafia.
元マフィアなんだって
The others were soldiers, but he was mafia!
皆兵隊だったのに　一人だけマフィア
一人目はウゴ君に　決定
I've decided Ugo will be our first target.
Shaojiang, please allow me
to work under you once more!
少将
どうか　もう一度私を少将の下で働かせてください
In our fights against the Hekmatyar siblings,
へクマティアル兄妹との戦い 二度の敗北
I lost both times!
Please give me the chance to restore my honor!
挽回するチャンスをください
Karen, please call me "Executive Director."
カレン
専務と呼んでくれ
People in this country are
sensitive about that word.
この国の人間はそういう単語に敏感だ
The country is constantly in civil war,
内戦ばかりの国情
even though they spend 80% of their
capital income on purchasing weaponry.
資本収入の80%を武器買いに費やすくせにな
I have said that those
minor failures do not bother me.
私はあの程度の失敗はかまわないと言ったんだ
The Da Xinghai Company belongs to me.
大星海公司は私のもの
Under this pretext, you two
are my civilian bodyguards,
君たちも名目上　中国軍を退役したん民間警備員
who have left the Chinese army.
But when the Central
Committee learned the fact
しかし全滅という事実を中央委員会が知ることとなり
that everyone had been annihilated,
they insisted that I let you go.
きみに暇を出せと口出ししてきた
That is the voice of my fatherland.
それは祖国の理性だ
I have no choice but to obey.
従う外はない
No! The very reason why
I follow you is fading away!
だめだ 私があなたについていく理由まで消えてしまおうとしている
You were the embodiment of battle and power.
戦闘と力の権化のような人だった
It is to our land's benefit that you fight.
あなたが戦うことが国の利益であり
You obeyed your battle instincts.
従っていたのは戦いの本能だった
That is the you I fell in love with.
その姿に私は惚れ込んだのに
I will do menial labor or whatever you like!
雑用でも何でもいいので 私を少将のそばにおいてください
Just please leave me by your side, Shaojiang.
Without your battles, what do you have left?!
あなたから戦いを取ったら　何が残るというんだ
Please give it a rest, Former Lieutenant Low.
いい加減にしてください　ロウ元・中尉
Oh, my apologies. You slipped in the mud.
あ　失礼
泥ですべりますよ
Li, you bastard...!
李　貴様　私より下級が
You're lower ranked than me!
No, I'm the same rank.
I was promoted to Lieutenant.
いいえ　同格です
中尉になりました
At any rate, Shaojiang will continue to fight,
それはおいておいて
少将の戦いは続きます あなたがいなくても
even if you are gone.
The Da Xinghai Company's
business ventures will continue to expand,
大星海公司の事業は拡大します
clear to the point where Shaojiang
will become China's image of Africa.
中国にとって少将がアフリカの象徴となるほど
My new unit shall protect Shaojiang.
少将は私の新たな部隊がお護りする
Shaojiang...
少将
I will come back again tomorrow.
また明日も来ます
Executive Director Chen
Guoming isn't as old as he looks.
陳国明専務は見た目ほどおじいさんじゃないっスよ
He just aged big time after he injured his leg.
足を悪くしてからガクッと老けたとのこと
He stepped on a mine in 2001.
2001年に地雷を踏んだっス
Go on.
続けて
Chen was the one who
attacked the patrol platoon
ヴェルマー少佐…
バルメさん率いるアンフィッド中隊
and the UNFID squad commanded
by Major Velmer--Valmet.
巡察小隊を襲撃したのは陳です
I'm sure of it.
間違いないっス
Supposedly he uses a really weird fighting style.
ずいぶん妙な戦い方をするとか
He runs straight to
the center of his enemy's forces
ナイフのついた拳銃を両手に敵のど真ん中をかけぬける
with knives attached to each of his guns.
Just hearing that made it
clear he's a battle junkie.
それ聞いただけで「戦うの大好きっ子」
走れなくなって老けちゃうのもさもありなんって感じっス
It's like, totally understandable that
he aged once he couldn't run anymore.
He distinguished himself through
his operations in Central Asia,
中央アジア工作で頭角を現した人物ですが
but possibly under order from military elites,
軍上層部の命令なのか
he started to hang around Africa in
the '90s, where his trail goes faint.
90年代　アフリカをうろちょろするようになってから
足跡がおぼろげになります
「とかげのしっぽ」になったと考えられるっス
It's conceivable that they
used him as a scapegoat.
つまり　大星海公司とは
In other words, Da Xinghai
Company is an independent division
meant to appease those in power so
they can mine for petroleum and natural gas.
石油　天然ガス採掘のための
有力者の懐柔
They handle infrastructure
security for oil refineries and pipelines,
製油所　パイプラインとのインフラ警備
negotiate and mediate terms between
the locals and the weapons industry,
兵器産業と現地の仲介　橋渡し
and deliver the local army's
military orders to the militia.
現地正規軍　民兵への軍事指導
いわゆる　ダーティーワークを薄－く手広―く行う独立部門
They spread themselves thin and
wide as they handle the dirty work.
They are the advance guard used to
increase their land's political influence.
本国の政治的影響力拡大のための尖兵です
My superior got enraged and said he'd
discern how Chen is making his fortune, but...
陳がどうやって儲けてるのか探ってやるってイキ巻いていた上司も
What the hell?! This is normal crap!
何これ　普通じゃん
He was so disappointed when he learned that.
それを知ってガッカリしちゃって
Now he snaps at anyone
who brings this topic up.
この話題出すと逆ギレします
I debated about whether or not
I should tell Valmet the results of my research.
バルメさんに調べた結果を伝えるか悩んだんスよ
Why? Isn't this precisely
the information Valmet wanted?
なんで
これこそバルメが知りたがってた情報でしょ
I have no idea what Valmet would think
私たちが知ってつまらない男のことをバルメが聞いて
after hearing about some
man that doesn't interest us.
何を思うのか
見当もつかない
When you called me out about Valmet,
バルメさんの件でって呼び出された時には
I came prepared to take a good whack from you.
1発殴られる覚悟できましたよ
Also, she said something like,
あと　彼女こんなこと言ってましたよ
"Thank you. Thanks to Koko,
I was able to unlock the world."
ありがとう　ココのおかけで世界の鍵が開きました
It is so strange.
不思議でなりません
I walked all around the world with Koko,
ココとさんざん世界を歩き回ったなのに
but in the end, I came back to
the country where it all started.
結局始まりの国に戻って来て
Is there something out here in the boonies?
こんな辺鄙なところに何かあるのかい
Uh, I'm going to say this since
you don't look like normal folk.
あのう　お客さんらどう見てもカタギじゃないから言うんだけど
No matter how confident
you are in your abilities,
いくら腕っ節に自信があっても
中華街には入らないほうがいいよ
you should stay clear of Chinatown.
"Chinatown"
The guys mining natural gas built
the town, but for some odd reason,
天然ガス掘ってる人たちが作った街なんだけど
なぜか民兵とか危ない人が集まるようになっちゃって
"Chinatown"
the militia and nasty ruffians
started to hang out around there.
It's so dicey that none
of the locals go near there.
おっかなくて　地元のもんは近づかないよ
So word spreads fast
when an outsider stumbles in.
余所者が入ってきたら　あっという間に知れ渡っちまう
Thank you for the warning.
ご忠告ありがとうございます
We'll take your advice.
おっしゃるとおりにしましょう
We'll get a hotel in the neighboring town.
隣町に宿を取ります
うん
っていうか　私たちカタギに見えませんか
Actually, we don't look like normal folk?
Not at all! Aren't you soldiers?
I can tell by your mannerisms.
ぜんぜん見えないけども
軍人さんでしょ
立ち振る舞で分かりるよ
I looked over the goods in
the trucks, Miss Hekmatyar.
トラックの品を確認したぜ
ミス・へクマティアル
Their quality is wonderful!
素晴らしいクォリティーだ
Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます
Now then, we shall give you the three
truck keys in exchange for the money.
では３台のキーと引きかえに
お代を頂戴いたします
ああ　はいはい
Oh, okay, okay...
This is high quality, pure stuff.
高純度の上物だ
Sell it just right and you will earn
way more than what we agreed upon.
うまく裁きゃ
約束の値段大きく超えるぜ
This is why I hate low-paying jobs.
これだから安い仕事は嫌なんだよ
You wouldn't pay in advance
when I asked you to, either.
先払いって言っても聞かないし
What? What are you going on about?
何だ　 何ブツクサ言ってやがる
I said to hand over the money.
How did you interpret "money" as "powder"?
金を出せと言ったのに
どう聞き違えれば粉になるんだ
Bitch!
テオー
What the hell are you doing?!
何やってんだ　テメエ
Boss!
ボス
ああ　リリアーヌとグレゴを連れて来なくて本当によかった
I'm really glad I didn't
bring Liliane and Grég along.
興奮して今やっちゃおうよとか言い出すに決まってます
I'm sure they'd get so excited that
they'd say, "Let's kill them now!"
They easily massacred
a group of 10 or so amateurs.
素人10人ぐらいは軽く瞬殺か
Well, that's no surprise or anything.
ま　意外でも何でもないですが
バルメとヨナがいないな
The one called Valmet isn't here.
What's up with that?
どういうことだ
かなりチャンスかもしれませんね
This might be our big chance.
Roger, Boss Dominique.
了解　ボス・ドミニク
Lili, he said to "Move out."
リリ　動けと
We're taking action?
出動？
Yahoo! What should I wear, Grég?
何着てこうかな　グレゴ
Wouldn't a black t-shirt
and black pants be appropriate?
黒いTシャツと黒いパンツがいいのでは
Roger!
ラジャー
Wasn't the boss supposed to always be smiling?
ボスってのは常に笑っているべき じゃなかったっけ
Isn't that what you promised him?
あいつとの約束は
Promises aren't meant to be kept at all times.
約束なんて常に守れるもんじゃないでしょ
You got it! I thought
the same thing after saying that.
だな　俺も言ってて思った
What's gotten into the Little Lady?
いったいどうしたんだ　お嬢は
どうしたも何もいつもどおりだろうが
Nothing's gotten into her.
She's the same as always.
What?! Think before you speak!
何だと
考えて物言えよ
じゃよォ　アール
So then, R, were we supposed to accept
their drugs and deal them out ourselves?
奴らの言いなりに物受け取って俺らが裁くか
We aren't drug dealers.
売人じゃねぇぞ　俺らはよ
Those mafia chose to do something
stupid and they chose to die.
このマフィアとも勝手に間抜けこいて勝手に死んだのさ
I think that the Little Lady
made the right decision.
俺はお嬢は間違ってねぇと考えてる
First, I noticed a difference in Valmet.
まず　バルメの異変に気づいた
I'm the one who ordered
Jonah to go with Valmet.
ヨナにバルメについていけと命じたのは私だ
I told him to accompany her if
she ever left without telling us.
彼女が黙って出て行くようなことがあったら…と
That was how I planned for this.
そのための準備も
Wow, most impressive.
I didn't notice the change.
ヘェ　さすがだなぁ
俺は気づかなかった
After all, Valmet's always acting weird.
だって　いつも変じゃん　バルメって
I think that sending
Jonah along will be effective.
ヨナ君を行かせたってのも効果ありだと思うしよ
I... I can't write Valmet off as
a mere soldier used for my protection.
私は
私にとってバルメは
もう一介の護衛の兵士とはいえない
I have spent more time
with her than my own parents.
そばにいた時間は親よりも長く
She is my sister, teacher, and
something more beyond that...
姉
教師
それ以上の何か
That's something you'd better not mention, Koko.
っていうのは口に出さねぇほうがいいな ココ
Soldiers put a lot of thought into
stuff like that when they fight.
兵隊は結構そういうの気にして戦ってるもんだ
"Is my boss worth risking my life for?"
俺のボスは命をかけるほどの奴か
"What am I worth?"
俺の価値は
I don't worry about it too much,
but there are some who will turn yellow
俺はあんまし気にしねーけど
ボス本人が早々に答えてやっちゃあ
if their boss up and gives them the answer.
安心してフ抜ける奴も出てきちまう
Sometimes acting oblivious
is part of your job, Koko.
時々には無神経を演じるのもココの仕事ってな
Got it?
Oh, jeez! What a waste of time!
あーあ　まったく無駄足を踏んだ
We're leaving!
帰るぞ
Okay!
ウェーイ ウメッ
That's good!
Bath time! Bath time!
お風呂　お風呂
さーて巡回始めますか
--Well, shall we begin our rounds?
--Sure.
おーう
--Fully loaded?
--Yep.
弾満弾？
おーう
Huh?
あれ
Damn it! Tojo, get in front
of the Little Lady's room!
クソ
東条　お嬢の部屋の前へ
Yeah!
あぁ
Lehm! Ugo! R!
レーム　ウゴ　アール
Two minutes.
2分です
Liliane, just throw them into turmoil.
リリアーヌはとにかく場をグチャグチャにする
Grég will take advantage of that to kill Ugo.
その隙にグレゴがウゴをやります
2分で引き上げですよ いいですね
Pull back in two minutes. Got that?
Not my butt again!
またケツ
Not another brat!
またガキかよ
Duck!
伏せろ
How many are there?!
何人だ
Unknown! There's one kid,
but there should be more!
不明
ガキ一人
もっといるはず
廊下に出るな
Don't enter the hallway!
--Wilee!
--Yep!
ワイリ
はい
Ugo!
ウゴ
--R!
--Yeah!
アール
おーう
--Mao!
--Yes!
マオ
はい
Lehm!
レーム
Ugo! Lehm!
ウゴ　レーム
You bastard--!
The ocean god reclines against the light,
光横たえる海神
光怪陸離的海底龍神
His mistake wavering along the scar
創痕の間に揺らめく過ち
累累創痕之間搖曳著縷縷罪孽
He rises to the surface and takes a breath
浮上して息を継ぎ
浮出水面 吸清吐濁
For he has obtained a love
and hate that only dissolve and blend
溶かされ混じるだけの憎愛を手にした
愛與恨 如漆似膠 如影隨形
His dream leans toward
矛盾孕む
矛盾誕生
The sound of the scheme
この世界ごと 覆い尽くしてる策動の音に傾く夢
冥冥的夢中 世界漸漸傾浸於欺言詭語之中
That shall encompass this
world fraught with contradictions
He no longer has legs
脚は　もう無い
足膝 已沒入虛無
His heartbeat pierces through the watery wall
水壁を貫く鼓動
透過水壁 傳來陣陣鼓動..
惡魔島字幕組(bbs.emland.net)
諸神字幕組(kamigami.org)
毀滅之丘 phase.2
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"
本字幕由   惡魔島字幕組   &   諸神字幕組   聯合制作
(bbs.emland.net)    (kamigami.org)
日聽 貓日和        日聽 框框
翻譯 TL舊民        校對 YAYA
後期 aoi         時軸 ZZZ
僅供交流學習之用 禁止用於商業用途
諸神字幕組
惡魔島字幕組